Capra Press mss., 1955-2010 LMC 2228
Lilly Library
- II. Capra Press publications
  - Brown, James Dale
    - The Sudden Disappearance of Japan, Proofs, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Bukowski, Charles
    - Fire Station, Proofs and artwork, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bunin, Ivan
    - Wolves and Other Love Stories, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Wolves and Other Love Stories, Printers MS, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Wolves and Other Love Stories, Proofs, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Burton, John
    - Collected Poems, Proofs, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Campbell, Grant
    - Words, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Words, MS, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Carrington, Leonora
    - The Oval Lady, Artwork and cover design, 1975 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
    - The Oval Lady, Artwork, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - The Oval Lady, MS and proofs, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Carson, Anne Conover
    - Caresse Crosby, Correspondence and misc. documents, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Caresse Crosby, MS, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 21-23)
    - Caresse Crosby, Proofs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Carver, Raymond
    - At Night the Salmon Move, Artwork, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - At Night the Salmon Move, MS, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - At Night the Salmon Move, proofs, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Back-to-Back #5, Carver MS, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
    - Back-to-Back #5, Carver page proofs, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Back-to-Back #5, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Back-to-Back #5, Le Guin MS, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
    - Back-to-Back #5, Proofs, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Fires, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Fires, MS, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
    - Fires, Original MS, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
    - Fires, Photos, 1983 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - Fires, Proofs, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Fires, Second proofs, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Furious Seasons, Artwork, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Furious Seasons, Galley proof, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Furious Seasons, MS, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Furious Seasons, Paste-ups, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Put Yourself in my Shoes, Art and proofs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Put Yourself in my Shoes, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Chamberlain, Jane
    - Saloons of San Francisco, Artwork, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Saloons of San Francisco, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Saloons of San Francisco, Financial records, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Saloons of San Francisco, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Saloons of San Francisco, MS, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Saloons of San Francisco, Proof, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Chambers, Stan
    - News at Ten, MS, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 6-8)
    - News at Ten, Proofs, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 9-10)
  - Chardenon, Ludo
    - In Praise of Wild Herbs, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - In Praise of Wild Herbs, Galleys, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - In Praise of Wild Herbs, MS, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - In Praise of Wild Herbs, MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - In Praise of Wild Herbs, Proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Christians, George S.
    - Don't Shoot In The Oilfields Carelessly, Artwork, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Don't Shoot In The Oilfields Carelessly, Book design material, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Don't Shoot In The Oilfields Carelessly, Galleys and page proof, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Don't Shoot In The Oilfields Carelessly, MS, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Codrescu, Andrei
    - A Serious Morning, Galleys, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - A Serious Morning, MS, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Coffin, Lewis A.
    - Children's Nutrition, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Children's Nutrition, First MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Children's Nutrition, MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - Children's Nutrition, Proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Children's Nutrition, Second MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - The Grandmother Conspiracy Exposed, Art and proofs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
    - The Grandmother Conspiracy Exposed, Edited MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The Grandmother Conspiracy Exposed, Galleys, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The Grandmother Conspiracy Exposed, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The Grandmother Conspiracy Exposed, Proofs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The Grandmother Conspiracy, Proofs, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Coover, Robert
    - Aesop's Forest and The Plot of the Mice, Art, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Aesop's Forest and The Plot of the Mice, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Aesop's Forest and The Plot of the Mice, MS, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Aesop's Forest and The Plot of the Mice, Page proofs, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Aesop's Forest and The Plot of the Mice, Proofs and galleys, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Craft, Christine
    - An Anchorwoman's Story, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - An Anchorwoman's Story, Galleys, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - An Anchorwoman's Story, Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - An Anchorwoman's Story, MS, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 10-12)
  - Crowther, C. Edward
    - Intimacy, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Intimacy, Galleys, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 14-16)
  - Curtis, Jack
    - Eagles over Big Sur, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Eagles over Big Sur, Misc., 1981 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Eagles over Big Sur, MS, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 24-25)
    - Eagles over Big Sur, Proofs, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Cushman, Dan
    - Voyagers of the Midnight Sun, Author's proofs, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Voyagers of the Midnight Sun, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Voyageurs of the Midnight Sun, Proofs, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 13-15)
  - Dale, Nancy
    - Flowering Plants, Book design materials, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Flowering Plants, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Flowering Plants, Galleys, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Flowering Plants, MS, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 18-20)
    - Flowering Plants, MS and illustrations, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - De Laittre, John
    - Peking Fortnight, MS, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - DeMille, Richard
    - Castanada's Journey, Artwork, 1977 (Box 60, Folder Unknown)
    - Castaneda's Journey, 2nd edition page proofs, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Castaneda's Journey, 2nd edition revisions, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Castaneda's Journey, Artwork, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Castaneda's Journey, MS, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13-15)
    - Castaneda's Journey, Permissions, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Castaneda's Journey, Promotional materials, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Castaneda's Journey, Proofs, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - The Royal Banquet, Artwork, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - The Royal Banquet, Galleys and page proofs, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - The Royal Banquet, MS, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Detro, Gene
    - Patchen, Cover art, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Patchen, MS, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Patchen, Proofs, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Di Prima, Diane
    - Loba, Proofs, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Dubin, Beverly
    - Water Squatters, Advertising, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Water Squatters, Artwork, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Water Squatters, Dummy, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 31-32)
    - Water Squatters, Dummy and proofs, 1975 (Box 59, Folder Unknown)
    - Water Squatters, Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Water Squatters, MS, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
    - Water Squatters, Releases, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Durand, Robert
    - The Book of Months, Artwork, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - The Book of Months, Galleys and dummy, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - The Book of Months, MS, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - The Old Man and the Monkey King, Artwork, 1972 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - The Old Man and the Monkey King, Bound MS, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - The Old Man and the Monkey King, MS, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - The Old Man and the Monkey King, Proofs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Durrell, Lawrence
    - Blue Thirst, MS, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Blue Thirst, Proofs, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Down the Styx, Artwork, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Down the Styx, MS of preface, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - The Paintings of Henry Miller, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - The Paintings of Henry Miller, MS, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - The Paintings of Henry Miller, text, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - The Plant Magic Man, Galley, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Dworski, Susan
    - Canvas Craft, Corrected galleys, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Canvas Craft, Misc., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Canvas Craft, MS, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    - Canvas Craft, Original artwork, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Canvas Craft, Proofs, 1979 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
  - Eastlake, William
    - Back-to-Back Volume XI, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Back-to-Back Volume XI, Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Back-to-Back Volume XI, MS, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 3-4)
    - Back-to-Back Volume XI, Printouts, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Back-to-Back Volume XI, Proofs, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Easton, Robert
    - China Caravans, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - China Caravans, Layout, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - China Caravans, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - China Caravans, MS, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - China Caravans, Proofs, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Guns Gold and Caravans, Cover design materials, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Guns Gold and Caravans, MS, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
    - Guns Gold and Caravans, Page proofs, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Guns Gold and Caravans, Paste-ups, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Guns Gold and Caravans, Press proofs, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Guns Gold and Caravans, Unbound press sheets, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Power and Glory, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Power and Glory, MS, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 4-6)
    - Power and Glory, Proofs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 7-8)
    - This Promised Land, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - This Promised Land, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - This Promised Land, MS, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
    - This Promised Land, Proofs, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - This Promised Land, Revisions, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Ehrlich, Gretel
    - Arctic Heart, Artwork, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Arctic Heart, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Arctic Heart, Dummies, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Arctic Heart, Page proofs, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - City Tales, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Drinking Dry Clouds, MS, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Drinking Dry Clouds, Proofs, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Geode, Galleys and page proofs, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Geode, MS and misc. documents, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Elder, Leon
    - Free Beaches, Artwork, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Free Beaches, Dummy, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Free Beaches, Galleys, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Free Beaches, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Free Beaches, Notes, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Waitress, Book design materials, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Waitress, Bound MS, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Waitress, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 22-23)
    - Waitress, Dummy, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Waitress, Ephemera, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Waitress, MS, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 21-25, 1-3)
    - Waitress, Photos, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 4-10)
    - Waitress, Photos and book design materials, 1985 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - Waitress, Research materials, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Waitress, Slides and film strips, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Ellsworth, Ron
    - Cat Hair Everywhere, MS and illustrations, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Empringham, Toni
    - Fiesta in Aztlan, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Fiesta in Aztlan, MS, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Fiesta in Aztlan, Proofs, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
    - Fiesta in Azatlan, Proofs with edits, 1982 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
  - Engberg, Edward
    - On Civilizing the Corporations, Cover art, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - On Civilizing the Corporations, MS, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - On Civilizing the Corporations, Proofs, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Eshleman, Clayton
    - Bearings, Proofs and cover design, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Evarts, Hal
    - Skunk Ranch to Hollywood, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Skunk Ranch to Hollywood, Final proofs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Skunk Ranch to Hollywood, Proofs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Everson, William
    - Who is She, Proofs and dummy, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Faber, Thomas
    - Learning to Love it, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Learning to Love it, Proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Fagan, Brian
    - California Coastal Passages, Book design materials, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - California Coastal Passages, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - California Coastal Passages, Misc., 1981 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - California Coastal Passages, Typesetting proposal, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, Galleys, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, Misc., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, MS, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 8-10)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, Page proofs, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, Paste-ups, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, Photographs, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Cruising Guide to the Channel Islands, Proofs, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Femling, Jean
    - Great Piers of California, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 9-10)
    - Great Piers of California, MS and proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Great Piers of California, Proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Fielding, Blair
    - Nothing But the Marvelous, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Nothing But the Marvelous, Permissions and MS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Nothing But the Marvelous, Proofs, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Fixel, Lawrence
    - Deserts of Snow, MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Deserts of Snow, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Francis, Eileen
    - The Birthday Book, Corrections, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Freeman, Joanne
    - Dreamscapes, the Collages of Joanne Freeman, Image proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Dreamscapes, the Collages of Joanne Freeman, Slides, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Dreamscapes, the Collages of Joanne Freeman, Text proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Gallagher, Tess
    - Portable Kisses Expanded, Proofs, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 1-5)
    - Portable Kisses, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Portable Kisses, Proofs, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Gebhard, David
    - Lutah Maria Riggs, MS, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Robert Stacy-Judd, Maya Architecture and the Creation of a New Style, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Robert Stacy-Judd, Maya Architecture and the Creation of a New Style, Proofs, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 7-10)
  - Gifford, Barry
    - Kerouac's Town, MS and photos, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gorey, Edward
    - Donald and the..., Correspondence, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Gover, Robert
    - Getting Pretty on the Table, MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Grace, Gregory
    - The Money of the Sunlight, Proofs, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Grant, Gordon
    - Journey, Galleys, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Gray, Virginia
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Book production materials, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Cover design material, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Original MS submission, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Photographs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Photographs (1/2), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Photographs (2/2), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Press proofs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Printer's MS, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Mud Space and Spirit, Proofs, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hamri, Mohamed A.
    - Tales of Joujouka, Artwork, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Tales of Joujouka, First MS, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Tales of Joujouka, Proofs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Harman, Dirk
    - Natives in Exile, Bound MS, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Natives in Exile, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Natives in Exile, Final MS, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 14-15)
    - Natives in Exile, Original art, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Natives in Exile, Proofs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Haslam, Gerald
    - California Heartland, Cover design material, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - California Heartland, MS, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
    - California Heartland, Proofs, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - California Heartland, Table of contents and intro, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Heintz, William
    - Wine Country, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Wine Country, Page proofs, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Wine Country, Proofs, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Heintzelman, Donald
    - The Wildlife Protector's Handbook, Correspondence and MS, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - The Wildlife Protector's Handbook, MS and proofs, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 10-13)
  - Hill, Eleanor
    - The Family Secret, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Hirschman, Jack
    - Cantillations, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Cantillations, Proofs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hoagland, Edward
    - The Final Fate of the Alligators, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - The Final Fate of the Alligators, Proofs, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Holmgren, Virginia
    - Owls, Art, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Owls, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Owls, MS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 12-13)
    - Raccoons, Illustrations, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Raccoons, MS, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 15-17)
    - Raccoons, Photos and captions, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Raccoons, Printer's MS, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Raccoons, Proofs, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Corrected proofs, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Correspondence and art, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Galleys, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 20-21)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Illustration prints, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, MS, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, MS revisions, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 1-5)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Page proofs, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Unbound pages, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - The Way of the Hummingbird, Uncorrected proofs, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 9-10)
  - Hopkins, Lee
    - After they learn to Dance, Artwork, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - After they learn to Dance, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
  - Houston, James
    - An Occurence at Norman's Burger Castle, Artwork, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - An Occurence at Norman's Burger Castle, Galleys, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - An Occurence at Norman's Burger Castle, MS, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - An Occurence at Norman's Burger Castle, Page proofs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Back-to-Back #3, MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
    - Back-to-Back #3, MS and uncorrected proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Back-to-Back #3, Proofs, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 16-19)
    - Gasoline, Corrected proofs, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Gasoline, Draft of final story, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Gasoline, Printer's MS for last story, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Gasoline, Promotional material, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Three Songs for my Father, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Three Songs for my Father, Proofs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Howorth, Peter
    - Foraging along the California Coast, Artwork and book design, 1977 (Box 60, Folder Unknown)
    - Foraging along the California Coast, Drawings and photos, 1977 (Box 60, Folder Unknown)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, Final proofs, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, First proofs, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, Galley proofs, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, MS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, MS for printer, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, Paste-ups, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
    - Foraging Along the Pacific Coast, Text for covers, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Hudson, W.H.
    - The Bird Biographies, Correspondence and MS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Islands Magazine Editors
    - Islands, A Treasury of Contemporary Travel Writing, Budapest MS, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Islands, A Treasury of Contemporary Travel Writing, Foreword, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Islands, A Treasury of Contemporary Travel Writing, Newfoundland MS, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Jacopetti, Roland
    - Rescued Buildings, Clippings and miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Rescued Buildings, Copies of illustrations, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Rescued Buildings, Final MS, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Rescued Buildings, Galleys, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Rescued Buildings, MS for printer, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Rescued Buildings, Original MS version (not used), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Rescued Buildings, Original photos and artwork, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Rescued Buildings, Outtakes, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Rescued Buildings, Page proofs, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Rescued Buildings, Page spreads, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Rescued Buildings, Royalties, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Rescued Buildings, Unbound publication, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Rescued Buildings, Working dummy and rough layout, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - James, Allston
    - Attic Light, Galleys, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Attic Light, Graphics of excerpt, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Attic Light, MS, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 17-18)
  - Kaysing, Bill
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, Artwork, 1974 (Box 58, Folder Unknown)
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, Misc., 1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, New ed. correspondence, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, New ed. MS, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21-22)
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, Photographs and proofs, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Great Hot Springs of the West, Reprint materials, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 6-10)
    - Great Hot Springs, Dummy, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Great Hot Springs, Galleys, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Great Hot Springs, MS, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Great Hot Springs, Photographs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28-29)
    - Great Hot Springs, Research, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Kelly, Frank
    - Starship Invincible, Book design materials, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Starship Invincible, Galleys, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Starship Invincible, Misc., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Starship Invincible, MS, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Starship Invincible, Original artwork, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Starship Invincible, Page proofs, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Starship Invincible, Xeroxes of 1930s edition, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Kicknosway, Faye
    - A Man is a Hook, Artwork, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - A Man is a Hook, Galleys, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)